我们在美丽的西班牙伊比沙岛
Here we are in beautiful Ibiza, Spain.
美丽的沙滩
Beautiful sand.
美妙的海浪
Beautiful waves.
穿着我最喜欢的那条短裤
My favorite shorts.
还有我最爱的女人 她马上就要成为...
And my favorite girl who is about to get...
我的天
Oh, my God!
嘿
Hey!
- 把那给我 - 别闹了
- Come on, give it to me. - No! Stop! Come on!
- 米奇 - 这拍的挺好嘛
- Mitch! - This is great!
我是认真的
I'm serious.
我的天 你真可爱
Oh. Oh, my God. That is so cute.
亲爱的
Honey, this is like...
让我拍一会嘛
Let me film for just a couple minutes.
- 我们就像在度蜜月一样 - 我的天
- It's like we're honeymooners. - Oh, my God!
度蜜月呢
♪ Honeymooners ♪
- 度蜜月?
"Honeymoon"?
- 对啊
Yeah.
我们还没结婚呢
We're not married.
卡特丽娜·哈珀
Katrina Harper...
你是我最好的朋友
You're my best friend in the whole world.
亲爱的 不要
Oh, my God. Babe, stop it. You're gonna make me...
如果你哭了 对我来说简直就像世界末日一般
If you get emotional, you're gonna kill me.
我尽量忍着
I'm trying to get through this, babe.
我爱你 你在我心里最重要
I love you, more than anything.
你愿意嫁给我么
Will you marry me?
我的天
Oh, my God!
我愿意
- Yes! - Yeah?
我愿意 米奇·拉普
Yes, Mitch Rapp.
我愿意嫁给你
I'll marry you.
抱歉 用一只手不太方便
Sorry, it's hard one-handed.
喜欢么 这是我妈妈的戒指
You like it? It was my mom's ring.
我喜欢它
I love it.
我喜欢你
I love you.
- 你还在录像么 我的天 - 是的
- I'm still... - Are you filming? Oh, my God!
是的 我在录像 我要把这些都录下来
Yeah, I'm still recording. I'm trying to get this.
不要嘛 米奇
Come on, Mitch!
就像把你这个样子录下来 现在懂了嘛
This is why I was filming now. You see, now you get it.
笑一个
Smile.
我去拿点喝的
I'm gonna get drinks.
- 好么 - 好
- Okay. - Yeah?
- 别去太久
Don't be too long.
- 不会的
I won't, I won't.
- 我爱你
I love you.
- 我也爱你
我会回来的
I'll be back.
我们在水里订婚了 喝点东西庆祝一下
Engagement drinks in the water, people.
谢谢
Oh. Thank you. Thank you.
很棒 亲爱的 有人给我们鼓掌
Very sweet, thanks. Babe, we're getting applause.
我爱你
I love you.
谢谢
Thank you.
你好
Hola. Como estas?
需要什么嘛
What can I get you?
能不能给我来两杯
Um, can I just get two drinks, please?
两杯 嗯...
Dos bebidas, if that's right...
我刚刚订了婚 需要点特别的东西
Um, I just got engaged, so something special.
随便喝点什么就行
It can be anything, though.
你真幸运 伙计 祝贺你
Oh, you lucky guy.
要烈一点的 行么
Oh, can they be kinda strong too? Is that cool?
谢了 伙计
Thank you, man.
不用这么烈吧
Oh, whoa. Maybe not that strong.
卡特丽娜！
Katrina!
Katrina?
卡特丽娜！
Katrina!
米奇
Mitch!
卡特丽娜！
Katrina!
兄弟 今晚怎么样了
How are you tonight my brother?
准备去度假
I am ready to go on vacation.
点击加密链接下载
Click encrypted link, then download file.
把你们全部炸上天
We're gonna fucking set your shit on fire, man!
去死吧 你们这帮混蛋
Fuckin' burn, motherfucker, burn!
致全世界的兄弟们
To our brothers across the globe...
来加入我们 对抗美帝国主义吧
Come join our fight against American imperialism.
让他们为 我们的亲人 我们的朋友
They will pay for the murder of our families,
我们的孩子之死 付出代价
our friends, and all children.
等着
Hold it, hold it, hold it.
兄弟 你现在心里是怎么想的
What is in your heart brother?
我想让我的双手沾满异教徒的鲜血
I want to bathe my hands in the blood of the infidels.
你的按键已经被记录了 快点回复
We are logging your keystrokes. Answer quickly.
谁在悲伤之年去世了
Who was taken in the Year of Sorrow?
哈吉扎 和 阿布塔里卜
Khadijah and Abu Talib.
在登霄之行中 谁和先知在一起
Who was with the Prophet for the Isra and Mi'raj?
大天使加百列
The Angel Gabriel.
停下 住手
All right, stop! Come on, man!
放开他 放开他
Let him go, let him go. Let him go, let him go!
放开他
Break it up. Let him go!
老兄 你脑子有问题吧
What the fuck is your deal, man?
快点 拉普 滚出去
That's it. You're done, Rapp. Get out.
他老是这样
He keeps doing this shit.
滚出去
Get out!
真是他妈美好的一天
Have a nice fucking day.
你他妈真是个疯子
You were out of line.
继续训练 快点
Back to work. Keep moving.
快回来
Get outta there!
你会把自己害死的 你个蠢货
You're gonna get yourself killed, you dumbass!
拉普 还要我再跟你说一遍么
Rapp, why I gotta tell you again?
抱歉 纳兹尔先生 我没注意到已经过10点了
Sorry, Mr. Nazir. I didn't realize it was past 10:00.
我尽量控制噪声
I'll try to keep it down.
别再做运动了
Yeah, enough with the sports.
明白了 谢谢您 纳兹尔先生
Copy that. All right. Thanks, Mr. Nazir.
海滩恐袭案嫌犯 阿德南·曼苏尔
他又上线了
He's up again.
你收到一条新信息 查看信息
你会来到这里么
Will you come here?
无论安拉在何处召唤我 我都能前往参战
Allah wills that I join the struggle wherever I am called.
的黎波里 利比亚
愿主的平安在你上!
要是我的话 我就不会选你了
If it were up to me, I would not have chosen you.
但他们可不这么认为了
But others have decided differently.
安拉指引着我们前进
Whomsoever Allah guides there is none to misguide.
先知妹妹的名字叫什么 愿她安息
What is the name of the sister of the Prophet, peace be upon him.
胡扎法·宾特·哈里斯
Huzafa bint Al-Haarith.
你错了
Wrong.
那不是他的妹妹
She was not the Prophet's sister.
她被尊为先知的妹妹
She is honored as the sister of the Prophet, peace be upon him...
因为他们都吮吸过先知母亲的乳汁
...because both suckled from her blood mother, Halimah al-Sa'diyah.
你为什么来这
Why have you come?
帮助 阿德南·曼苏尔完成他的使命
To help Adnan al-Mansur achieve his people's destiny.
如果真主愿意的话
Inshallah.
我要你看着我的眼睛说
I wanted to look in your eyes.
我不信任你
I don't trust you.
我已经准备好成为殉道者了
I'm prepared to die a martyr.
我要怎么样才能赢得你的信任
What can I do to earn your trust?
不
No!
快让开
Step away, now!
别打了
Come on!
放开我
The fuck off me!
他已经死了 结束了
He's dead, it's over.
冷静 冷静
Easy. Easy. Take it easy.
本区域安全
Area's secure.
你想杀了他们 过去把他们都杀了
You wanted to kill them all, and then go on killing.
是不是挺极端的
Pretty extreme, don't you think?
我觉得一点也不极端
No, I don't think that's extreme at all.
他们这样的人
I think people like that deserve to die
就得让他们死的很难看
in the worst ways you can imagine.
关于你父母的死 你还记得多少
What do you remember about your parents' death?
那是一场车祸
Car crash.
我当时在马萨诸塞州
I was in Massachusetts.
他们在突尼斯
They were in Tunisia at the time.
当时14岁
I was 14.
我只记得这些
That's what I remember.
你的行为举止方面有些问题
You started having discipline problems.
曾被三个寄宿学校退学
Got yourself kicked out of three boarding schools.
我知道 只是不知道为什么会这样
Yeah, yeah. I know. I wonder what that was about.
谈谈那个沙滩上发生的事
Let's talk about what happened after that day on the beach.
我的天 又谈这个 你在逗我么?
Oh, Jesus Christ. Again? Are you kidding me?
是的 又谈这个
Yeah, again.
你在那之后是不是就自暴自弃了
You gave up everything after that, didn't you?
你本科在布朗大学就读
Your grad studies at Brown University.
我失去了兴趣
I must have lost interest.
对一切都失去了兴趣?
In everything?
不 不是这样
No, not everything.
再见 费雷恩博士
See you later, Dr. Frain.
明天 同一时间见面么
See you tomorrow, same time?
换个新面孔来见你
I like the new look.
我是艾琳·肯尼迪
Irene Kennedy, CIA Deputy Director
中情局反恐部副主任
in charge of Counterterrorism.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
你知道你在这呆了多久么
Any idea how long you been here?
30天
30 days.
够你想通一些事了
Enough time for you to figure out a couple things.
是啊 关于我自己的事 我想通了不少
Yeah, yeah. I've figured out a lot about myself.
过的很充实 谢谢
It's been a very reflective time. Thank you.
当时在现场你可能撑不过20秒
You wouldn't have made it through the next 20 seconds there alive.
天知道呢
I guess we'll never know now, will we?
你告诉费雷恩博士 说你要杀掉曼苏尔
You told Dr. Frain you thought you were gonna kill Mansur
扫平他的老巢
and wipe out his whole cell.
这只是个开始
For starters.
米奇 你心里还打着更大的算盘吧
You had an even bigger agenda, didn't you, Mitch?
你是怎么想的
What did you think,
你想一个又一个扫平恐怖分子的据点?
you were gonna jump from cell to cell taking out terrorists?
铲奸除恶?
Righting the world's wrongs?
我这不是搞定了曼苏尔么
Got to Mansur, didn't I?
比你有能耐啊
I mean, it's more than you accomplished.
我要跟你说一些事
I'm gonna let you in on something.
我们这的人不知道要拿你怎么办
Our people here, they don't know what to do with you.
很多人就觉得把你扔进一个高级别监狱就行了
A lot of them think we should just throw you in a supermax.
至于我嘛
Me?
米奇 我对你的计划很感兴趣
I like your agenda, Mitch.
如果你加入我们 我可以帮你实现你的目标
I can help you with it, if you throw in with us.
我们甚至可以把你培养成专业的特工
We can teach you how to play with the big boys.
让我先打断你一下
Yeah, let me stop you right there.
您认为我18个月前没考虑过
You don't think I considered that 18 months ago?
加入中情局么
Joining the CIA?
我觉得自己一个人行动干掉曼苏尔
I made the decision to pursue Mansur on my own
是因为我觉得我自己能办到
'cause I knew I could get it done.
你要明白 只有我才能帮你
What you need to understand is that I'm the only way.
达成你的目的
To get what you want.
为什么我要相信你
Why the hell would I trust you?
因为我相信你
Because I believe in you.
你只能指望我了
And I'm all you've got.
已确认
What's been confirmed is
一个退役的俄国
the enriched plutonium has been stolen
核设施里的浓缩铀遭窃
from a decommissioned Russian nuclear facility.
如果他们找到一个核起爆器
If they get their hands on a nuclear trigger
再找一个能造核弹的物理学家
and a physicist to build it,
他们就能装备核武器 引爆核弹
they'd be able to arm it and detonate it at any time.
汤姆?
Tom?
他的测试结果十分优秀
He's testing through the roof.
我从没见过这么厉害的
Might be the best I've ever seen.
我们监控了他6个月
We've had him under surveillance for six months.
关注了他的格斗术 枪法
Martial arts, gun skills.
我以前监控过不少这种民间人员
I've surveilled dozens of these vigilantes.
他很与众不同
This one is different.
艾琳 这些情况我都清楚
Yeah, well, I've gone over these, Irene.
他不服从命令 难以控制
He's noncompliant, he's oppositional.
我们跟着他找到了曼苏尔的老巢
He got us into Mansur's cell.
比我们强太多了
That's a hell of a lot more than we ever managed.
猎户星是我们这的
All right, Orion is an elite unit, Irene.
秘密精英特种部队
A secret unit.
只向你我二人报告
Reports to you, me, and no one else.
我不想为这人
I don't want to be responsible
可能闹出的乱子负责
for that kind of mistake.
你说话的语气和赫尔利一样啊
Now, that's Hurley talking.
他给我打了两次电话 就谈这个
Yeah, well, he's called me twice about this.
这样的人能把他吓坏
This kind of psych profile scares the hell out of him.
他估计会觉得
As far as he's concerned,
你给他派了个一心想复仇的疯子
you're sending him a Section 8 with an ax to grind.
在沙滩上发生的事
What happened to that kid on the beach,
改变了他的一生
it changed him.
就算通过训练 你也不可能对任何人起那么大的影响
You can't train that into someone.
他现在的心理状况正是我梦寐以求的
His psych profile is exactly what I've been looking for.
做过测谎仪测试么
Polygraph?
完美通过
Flying colors.
那就祝赫尔利好运吧
All right. Good luck with Hurley.
艾琳
Oh, Irene.
我们两个小时内会收到
We'll have fresh intel on the Russian
关于俄罗斯浓缩铀事件的情报
plutonium situation in two hours.
保持电话联系
Stay by your phone.
罗阿诺克峡谷 弗吉尼亚
你可以把眼罩摘下来了
You can take the blindfold off.
- 关于这家伙 有什么我要知道的?
So, what do I need to know about this guy?
- 你是说斯坦·赫尔利么
Stan Hurley.
他是个勇士
He's a warrior.
前海豹突击队特种兵
Ex-Navy SEAL.
我父亲和他一起在波斯湾服役过
My daddy served with him in the Persian Gulf.
你负责这个项目么
Did you go through this program?
我只是了解情况 不负责这个计划
I went through a program. Not this one.
这个计划不只是培养一个间谍
It's not like becoming a spy or Special Ops,
或者特工那么简单
none of those things.
知道了
Good.
米奇·拉普的心理报告
米奇 你的目标是什么
So, what are your goals, Mitch?
我的目标?
My goals?
我的目标就是如果他们知道我要来了
My goal is to have them lie awake at night,
会吓得睡不着觉
knowing I'm coming for them.
你不抽烟了?
I thought you were supposed to be on the patch.
- 你看了他的测试结果么
You saw those tests.
- 看了
Yeah, I saw them.
十分优秀
He's off the charts.
优秀的人我也见过
I've seen off the charts before.
军队出身的人员可能会养成一些难以摆脱陋习
And he's got none of the bad habits
然而他就不必了
he'd have to unlearn if he had military training.
难以摆脱?
Unlearn?
斯坦
Come on, Stan.
让你手下的那些海豹突击队进大城市里试试
You drop one of your Navy SEALs in an urban setting,
周围的人能轻松发现他们是当兵的
you can spot the boot camp on them a mile away.
- 现在不是..
We're not fighting the...
- 不是冷战那时候了 我知道
Cold War? Yeah, I know.
副主任女士 你一直在提醒我这点
You keep telling me that, Miss Deputy Director.
我的天 你这么尊敬我了
Oh, wow. "Miss Deputy Director."
你父亲会支持我这么做的
Your daddy would agree with me.
我每48小时联系你一次
I'll be checking in with you every 48 hours.
我早上坐飞机去伦敦
I'm on a plane to London in the morning.
赶紧去抽几根吧
And go back on the patch, for God's sake.
别让我失望
Don't prove me wrong.
她不会回来了
She ain't coming back.
嘿
Hey.
看着我
Eyes front and center.
抱歉
Sorry.
抱歉? 你以为我是你的大学教授么
"Sorry"? Do I look like one of your college professors?
小子 你要称呼我为"长官"
You talk to me, you call me "sir," son.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
你他妈的来这干什么呢
What the fuck you doing here?
是不是
Did you have some bad things happen to you,
有一些不幸的事发生在你身上
some shitty things happen to you?
你想把那些恐怖分子赶尽杀绝
Now you wanna kill those mean old terrorists.
就是那些你口中所谓的“坏人”
Go get some bad guys.
你凭什么认为
What makes you think you can make it
你能通过我的选拔?
through my selection process?
- 我能说话么 长官
Permission to speak, sir?
- 说吧 有话直说
Sure, go ahead if you got something to say.
因为你来这 就是个错误
Like this is all a big mistake and you wanna go home.
你想回家么
You wanna go home? Good.
赶紧滚吧 要不然我帮你滚
Get the fuck out of here. I'll drive you myself.
不想 长官
Not at all, sir.
我觉得我们还是直入主题吧
I was gonna suggest we maybe speed this whole thing up?
我们俩过几招
My guess is, if you and I go hand-to-hand,
我能否通过
you could probably figure out inside of 20 seconds
你的选拔
whether or not I have what it takes to make it
一看便知
through your selection process.
您觉得呢
So, what do you think?
给你一张床 一个储物柜
We got an empty cot, empty footlocker.
看你够不够格留在这里了
They're both yours as long as you can last.
我觉得可以
Sounds good.
跟我来
Follow me.
待会见
See you out there.
顺便说一句 我听说了不少关于你的事
Heard a lot about you, by the way.
想看看你有多大的能耐
Excited to see what you got.
来杀我
Kill me.
总有人以为这样就能要我的命
People think you can slice a man's throat like this.
只有拍电影才可能这么容易
That's only in the movies.
就是这
Right there.
用力压下去
Do it.
不会有动静 不会搞成乱摊子
No noise. No mess.
维克多 你来
Victor, you're up.
我操
What the fuck, man?
谁他妈带了把刀
Who grabs a fucking blade?
上啊
Come on, you fuckin' pussy. Let's go!
应该注意到后面的情况
You gotta have eyes in the back of your head.
你犹豫一下 就死了
You flinch, you die.
猎户座计划的核心就是完成任务
Orion is about the mission.
能者就上
It ain't about you.
你要是战死沙场 你就是个孤魂野鬼
You go down out there, you're a ghost, you don't exist.
没有人会回来救你的
There's nobody, nobody coming back for you.
要是你被俘了
You're about to be captured.
那就告别这个世界吧
Bye-bye.
伊朗大使馆 伦敦
我们现在了解到
We now know 15 kilos of plutonium-239
俄罗斯那边有15千克的钚-239不翼而飞
went missing during the Russian breach.
足够造一个核武器了
It's enough to build a full-scale nuclear weapon.
但可能需要倾全国之力才能完成核武器的建造
But that would likely require the resources of a nation-state.
作为伊朗参谋总长
As Iranian Chief of General Staff,
我们对此事同样关切
I share your concern.
我们同你们一样 都在关注事态发展
We have been monitoring the situation as you have.
我们也不知道是什么情况
I'm afraid we too are in the dark.
对伊朗来说 建造核武器
For Iran, of course,
是不可能的
a nuclear weapon is off the table.
我们签订了条约的
We have a treaty.
有一些伊朗人对这个条约不太满意
You have countrymen who are not too happy about that.
我们监控了你们的浓缩项目
We monitor your nuclear enrichment program pretty closely,
发现有人在俄罗斯黑市上购买了这些钚-239
but black market plutonium-239 from Russia...
关于黑市的情况 高层无从得知
Would be difficult for inspectors to detect.
您是肯尼迪女士 对吧?
Ms. Kennedy, yes?
作为伊朗国防部长 我向您保证
I assure you as Minister of Defense
我们知道如果我们伊朗
that we in Iran recognize how much the spirit of comity
通过任何途径购买钚燃料
between our nations would be compromised
都会影响到我们的国家利益
if we were to acquire
有违国际精神
weapons-grade plutonium from any source.
的确如此
Yes, it would.
这话对伊朗境外的势力同样适用
Same goes for your clients outside Iran,
真主党 哈马斯
Hezbollah. Hamas.
胡塞武装
The Houthis.
无论在谁的手中 核武器都是危险的
Nuclear weapons are a danger in any hands, Director.
这不就是你们入侵
Wasn't that your pretext for your invasion
我们邻国的理由么
of our neighbor to the west?
50万伊拉克人丧生
One that cost 500,000 Iraqi lives
留下一片废墟
and left a wake of destruction
整个地区至今动荡不安
from which our region has never recovered.
罗斯塔米将军 我们是掌握了确凿的情况才来这会面的
General Rostami, we came only to tell you what we know.
你们这算是威胁我们么
Is that a threat?
当然不是 比赫兹部长
Of course not, Minister Behruz.
各位先生 感谢参加这次会面
Gentlemen, I very much appreciate you meeting with us.
客气了
Not at all.
- 很遗憾 不能给你们提供更多情报
I only wish we could offer more insight.
- 谢谢您的支持
Thank you.
我不相信那个罗斯塔米将军
I don't trust General Rostami.
我们要低调行事
We need to keep this quiet.
猎户座计划进行的怎么样了
How ready is Orion?
我去问问赫尔利
I'll check in with Hurley.
为什么好几个小时了都没人来
Why is there no one on watch?
你们死定了
You're all dead.
是啊 是啊 知道了
Yeah, yeah. I got it, I got it.
你死了
You're dead.
你想说什么 快说啊
You wanna say something to me? Say it. Go on, say it.
给你们30秒收拾
You got 30 seconds!
这些是你们的目标
These are your targets.
记住他们
Memorize them.
你们要能辨认出他们来
It's your responsibility to be able to identify them.
杀掉一个武装人员 得一分
You shoot a combatant, you get a point.
没击中的话 会受到一次电击
You miss, you get a shock.
非战斗人员 会受到更强的电击
You shoot a noncombatant, you get a bigger shock.
如果武装人员击中了你
Combatant shoots you...
我就这么说吧 你那时候会感觉到的
Let's just say you're gonna feel it.
准备好了吗
Ready?
开始
Go.
赫尔利在干什么
What's Hurley doing?
他脑子出问题了
He's fucking with his head.
操
Fuck!
这狗屁的模拟训练
Fucking AR bullshit.
华沙 波兰
我们开始吧
Shall we?
好
Okay.
挺不错的
That's clever.
钚原料
Raw plutonium.
之前商量好的 是浓缩的
Highly enriched, as promised.
希望如此
Let's hope.
先生们 听到仪器发出响声真是太棒了
Wow, that's a beautiful sound, gentlemen.
那我就拿走了
May I?
嗯
Okay.
快转账
Wire the money.
马上就转
That, I can do.
我就拿手机
This is a cell phone.
把你的车开走 有一个重要官员要经过这里
Gotta move all the vans. The Cardinal's visiting.
好的
Okay.
五分钟内就走
Okay. Five minutes.
车里的是什么
What's going on in there?
纪念品
Souvenirs.
可能是紧急情况 请求增援
Possible code red, backup needed.
别紧张 没什么情况
There's nothing going on.
进来看看嘛
Come in.
目前看来
It now appears that all seven victims
7名死者
were shot with a single weapon,
死于同一把手枪下
believed to be a Glock 29.
车内发现了武器级钚的踪迹
Traces of weaponized plutonium
同时还发现了
were detected inside the van
三具俄罗斯人
where the bodies of three Russians
和两具波兰警察的尸体
and two Warsaw police officers were found.
俄罗斯政府已经确认
The Russian government has confirmed
核燃料的化学指纹表明
that the chemical footprint of the plutonium in question
这正是托博尔斯克
is a match to the plutonium that was stolen
废弃核设施内
from the decommissioned
失窃的钚燃料
processing facility in Tobolsk.
波兰警方正在和国际刑警组织合作
Security footage is being analyzed by Polish police,
分析监控录像
now working in conjunction with Interpol,
试图确认枪手的身份
to identify the shooter and his connection
调查他与钚燃料失窃案之间有何联系
to the missing plutonium.
枪手的身份尚不得知
The identity of the shooter remains unknown...
你好 打扰一下
Hi, excuse me.
有什么我能帮你的
- How can I help you? - Question.
目标 活动中
- 需要我帮你么
May I help you?
- 不 谢谢
No, thanks. I'm okay.
嘿
- Ow! Ow! Ow! - Hey! Hey! Hey!
拉普 妈的
Rapp! God damn it!
你要控制住自己
You have to stay under control.
妈的
Dickhead!
这家伙不知道什么时候住手
Asshole doesn't know when to quit.
你在逗我么 我刚刚救了你
You're kidding me, right? I just saved your ass.
拉普 你要知道什么时候该停手
You've gotta know when the mission's been accomplished, Rapp.
- 长官 这家伙.. - 听着
- Sir, he's a fucking... - Which he did.
别以为你只有眼前这一个目标
Never assume your target is the only target.
敌人可能看起来没什么威胁 但实际上心狠手辣
The enemy dresses like a deer and he kills like a lion.
我们也要像他们一样心狠手辣
And that's what we gotta do.
希望你能表现更出色
We just gotta do it better.
那就这样吧
All right.
你这混蛋
You're an asshole.
出事了
We got a problem.
六周前 有人闯入
Six weeks ago, there was a breach
俄罗斯的一个废弃钚燃料设施
at a decommissioned Russian plutonium facility.
我听说了
I'm aware.
但是你不知道 有15千克的钚燃料失窃了
What you don't know is 15 kilos of plutonium went missing.
还是武器级的
Weapons-grade.
这么多
That's a shit-ton of plutonium.
就这么落入他人之手
And it just changed hands.
我想给你看点东西
I wanna show you something.
看看这个
Take a look at this.
你应该认识这张脸吧
Does that face bong a gong for you?
还是只有我一个觉得这人很熟悉
Or is it just me?
不可能是他
It can't be him.
在轰炸了巴马科的大使馆之后 我们派出无人机又确认了一次
Our drones took him out after the embassy bombing at Bamako.
我们无法完全确定尸体身份
We never got a positive ID.
那是我们这的叛逃特工
That's our mad dog out there.
那行 我们先假设是他
All right. Let's say it's him.
艾琳 不用假设 就是他
It's him, Irene.
现在有一个一石二鸟的机会
This gives us a chance to kill two birds with one stone.
哈姆迪·沙里夫
Hamdi Sharif.
他是一个武器贩子 目前在土耳其
He's an arms dealer working out of Turkey.
四周前他买了一个俄罗斯设计的核装置起爆器
Four days ago, he purchased a Russian-designed nuclear trigger.
他肯定打算把这玩意转手
And he's gonna be selling it.
沙里夫手上有诱饵
Sharif's got the honey.
我们只需等待猎物上钩
Now we just wait for the bee.
我们派人破坏他们的交易
We go in, we fuck up their deal.
把他们都干掉
And we take 'em both out.
你去伊斯坦布尔
You're going to Istanbul.
我们那边有特工接应
We have an agent in place.
她会在机场接你
She'll meet you at the airport.
明白
All right.
安妮卡·奥格登
Annika Ogden. We've had her on the ground over there
她在那潜伏5年了
for five years.
让拉普参与这次行动
I want Rapp on the team.
你没开玩笑吧
Really?
斯坦 他已经准备好了吧
He's ready, Stan.
艾琳 我觉得他目前还没准备好
Actually, Irene, he's not ready.
但我会让他准备好的
But he will be.
长官 找我有事么
You wanted to see me, sir?
对 把门关上
Yeah. Shut the door.
我们有任务了
We're shipping out.
把东西放桌上
Set those down there.
你喜欢看电影么
You like movies?
喜欢
Sure.
我想给你看点东西
I got something for you.
这他妈是什么鬼
What the fuck is this?
- 我也觉得挺操蛋呢
Yeah, I thought so.
- 你说什么
You thought so?
- 是啊
Yeah.
你为什么大难不死呢 拉普
Why are you even alive, Rapp?
你有没有问过自己这个问题
You ever asked yourself that?
为什么是你 而不是这些人
Why you? You know, of all those people?
我觉得 肯定是因为你很特别
You're special, I guess.
我的天
Oh, my God!
需要我调高音量么
You want me to turn it up?
- 我愿意嫁给你 - 拿着吧
- I'll marry you! - Take it!
你这混蛋 把视频关上
You're a fucking coward, you know that? Turn that shit off.
这是我妈妈的戒指 你觉得怎么样
What do you think? It's my mom's ring.
关掉
You gonna turn it off?
卡特丽娜!
Katrina!
我是不是应该为你感到遗憾
Am I supposed to feel sorry for you?
我觉得还是不吧
I don't.
你犯了大错
You made a big mistake.
你让情绪影响到了你的判断力
You let emotion cloud your judgment.
永远不要受制于自己的情绪
Never, ever let it get personal.
明白了么
You understand?
我明白了
Yeah, I got it.
准备好 早上5点出发
Be ready to go by 5:00.
我们4点半见面
See you at 4:30.
伊斯坦布尔 土耳其
You know what you're gonna do here?
我知道我们来这干什么吗
No, sir.
- 不知道 长官 - 嗯
Correct. You don't.
多观察 少说话
So keep your eyes open and your mouth shut.
听我命令
And wait for my orders.
哈姆迪·沙里夫 房地产大亨 武器贩子
Hamdi Sharif, a real-estate mogul/arms dealer.
养活了不少恐怖分子
He's like Santa Claus for terrorists.
一个人渣
Scumbag.
小子 省省你那些
Spare me your junior-year-abroad
幼稚的看法吧
moral opinion, would you, Rapp?
长官 这不只是我的个人看法而已 他就是个人渣
Not really an opinion, sir. Sharif's a piece of shit.
我们这不是圣战
It's not a crusade.
任务以实用为重 不要受制于...
This mission is practical. Don't make it...
个人情绪?
Personal?
没错
Exactly.
明白 长官
Yes, sir.
维克多 你跟我一起
Victor, you're with me.
拉普和安妮卡 你们注意观察情况
Rapp, you and Annika are eyes on.
沙里夫日常生活很规律
Sharif has a routine.
看看他最近有什么异常
Let's see if anything breaks his pattern.
- 明白了么 - 是 长官
- Got it? - Yes, sir.
我们有48小时完成任务
All right, we got 48 hours.
要做的干净利索 不留痕迹
Quick, clean. No footprint.
这里的各股势力也是错综复杂的
This town's ready to blow as it is.
你要去哪
Where the hell are you going?
抱歉
Excuse me.
解密进行中
- 这他妈太冒进了
That was fucking reckless, Rapp.
- 长官 我这是主动出击
I took the initiative, sir.
- 可能会搞砸的 - 但我完成了
- He could've been made. - Well, I wasn't.
结果出来了
Here we go.
明天上午11点
11:00 a.m. tomorrow.
同他的情妇见面之前
A meeting at a restaurant on Akbiyik Street.
他会去阿克比克街的餐馆
That's right before Sharif goes to see his mistress.
这不符合他平时的日程
That breaks his pattern.
更关键的是
I'll tell you what'll break his pattern.
当他的助理告诉他手机丢了
When that fucking assistant tells his boss
那就糟糕了
he lost his goddamn phone.
他不会说的
He won't.
他太怕沙里夫了 不敢告诉沙里夫自己搞砸了
He's too afraid of Sharif to let him know he screwed up.
那行 我们明天行动
All right. We go tomorrow.
任务目标是?
What's the mission, sir?
干掉买家 干掉卖家
Eliminate the target. Eliminate the recipient.
带走货物
Obtain the package.
- 货物是什么
And what's the package?
- 到时候就知道了
We'll know it when we see it.
你打头阵
You're lead.
你做后援
You're backup.
我们在街对面监视现场情况
We will watch from across the street.
我们俩扮演一对情侣
We get to play lovers.
你们俩相恋多久了
How long have you been married?
他以为我们已经结婚了
He thinks we're married.
别想太多
Don't think too much.
你会紧张过头的
You'll lose your nerve.
我觉得不会
No, I don't think so.
这是你第一次参加任务么
It'll be your first time.
在我的脑海中 我已经参加了很多次任务了
Yeah, not in my mind.
老大 目标来了
Lead, your friend's arriving now.
收到
Copy.
真他妈的是军队级别的保护啊
And he brought a shitload of military protection.
我来搞定他们
I'll take care of the MPs.
亲爱的 别发火嘛
Oh, come on, now, honey. Don't be mad.
不不不
No, no, no.
我还有点事 真的
I had a few. Yeah, I did.
我回家后会给你补上的
I'll make it up to you when I get home.
你懂的
You know that.
贝勒贝伊宫附近发现汽车炸弹
Car bombing, near Beylerbeyi Palace.
把这条消息汇报上去 要不然我就割破你的喉咙
Call it in. Call it in, or I'll cut your fucking throat.
开始行动
Lead, you're a go.
二号 进入指定位置
Survey 2, get in place.
- 小心点 - 我知道的
- Be careful in there. - I got it.
抱歉
Pardon.
起爆器在轿车里
The nuclear trigger is in the sedan.
目标逃走了
Target's gone. Target's gone.
快走
Get back!
情况如何
Lead?
已死亡
Dead.
任务结束
Mission terminated.
撤到安全地点 已确认
Exfil to secure location. Confirm.
二号 快点他妈的确认执行命令
Survey 2, you better let me hear you fucking confirm.
妈的 乱成一团了 我们撤
God damn it, this is a fucking mess. We're out of here.
老实点
Drive! Drive!
跟着你们的老大
Follow your boss!
别杀我 我是他的助手
Please, I'm just the assistant!
别杀我
Don't hurt me!
快开车
Drive! Drive!
他住这的五楼
He's there right now on the fifth floor.
他做的事我也不喜欢
Please I don't approve of what Sharif does.
别杀我
Don't kill me.
别担心 我不会杀你的
Don't worry, I'm not gonna hurt you.
我的目标是你的老板
I'm gonna hurt your boss.
起爆器现在在美国人手上
The American mercenary has the nuclear trigger.
我搞定了我的任务 你搞定你的
I've done my job. It's your problem now.
妈的
Shit.
动作快点
Hurry up!
快滚开
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on.
求求你
No, please.
别杀我
Please, don't. Don't.
求求你
No.
中情局安全屋 罗马尼亚
你违背了我的命令
You disobeyed a direct order.
不 我决定追踪目标
No, I made a decision to pursue the target,
完成任务
and I completed the mission.
我来这就是为了完成任务
And, sir, isn't that what I'm here to do? Isn't that my job?
我他妈的要你干什么 你就干什么
Your fucking job is to do what I fucking tell you to do!
那就是说 你更倾向于让我离开那
What, you prefer I leave him alive, then,
放那人渣一马咯
let him go? That piece of shit?
斯坦
Stan?
太好了 你来了 我想给你看点东西
Good, you're here. I wanna show you something.
在那等着
Wait here.
你看 这么下去
Look at that. That's the kind of bullshit
这家伙会搞砸的
that could shut us down.
这小子不会遵守命令
Kid can't even follow a fucking order.
维克托没办到的事 拉普办到了
Victor got made. Rapp didn't.
他妈的 你为什么这么看好这个小子
Why does this kid give you such a fucking hard-on?
别他妈的跟我这么说话 我是你的上级
Don't talk to me like that! I'm your superior.
我的上级? 艾琳
My superior, Irene?
正是你的上级 妈的
Your superior, God damn it.
你知不知道 我花了多久才找到
Do you have any idea how long I spent looking
这么有才 这么有胆识的小伙子
for someone with that kid's talent and balls?
- 让拉普留下
Rapp stays.
- 这是命令么
You're giving me an order?
没错
That's an affirmative.
让我跟他单独谈会
Can you give us a minute?
看看这个
Look at this.
起爆器肯定在那辆车上
The trigger must have been in that car.
看看
Look at him.
就是他
Lookin' at me.
这家伙干出来的好事
Everything he did there,
都是我教出来的
I taught him how to do it.
斯坦
Stan.
我真不应该把他从海军里招过来
I should've left him in the Navy.
- 我要亲手杀了他
I'm gonna kill that son of a bitch.
- 斯坦 听我说
Stan, listen to me.
重要的是
The only thing that matters now
这个疯子已经拿到了
is that fucking lunatic has everything he needs
制取核武器的全部环节
to build a nuclear weapon.
他拿到了起爆器 现在要买通一个物理学家
He's got a trigger. Now he needs to buy a physicist.
你现在要搞清楚
We just have to figure out
他们要在哪造核武器
where they're gonna build this thing.
本
Ben.
拉普从沙里夫家拿到的那台笔记本电脑
That computer our boy Rapp lifted from Sharif's house,
显示 有一笔两百万美元的款项
there's evidence of a $2 million transfer to a bank account in Rome.
打到了一家罗马银行的账户上 等待支取
Cash prepped for withdrawal.
那我们去罗马
Rome.
考维尔建筑工地 罗马市附近
这是你的钱
Your money.
部长 我最近读了一些东西
I've been reading up, Minister.
你们伊朗人可能从小时候起就知道了
You Iranians probably all learn this growing up,
签订禁核条约前心里就有数了
or at least you did before you signed that treaty.
我没想到还有这么些有趣的情况
But me, I had no idea about these fun facts.
要是你的话我就不会进去
Yeah, I wouldn't do that if I were you.
起爆点三英里半径内的人都会蒸发掉
Inside three miles, apparently you just vaporize.
有一些幸免于难
Some folks don't.
他们的皮肤会被烤黑 烧焦
They get all black and charred,
扭曲成一团 没人知道为什么会成这个样子
and dense as lead, and no one knows why.
五英里半径内 热浪席卷一切
Inside five miles, everything is sucked into a void,
温度比太阳中心还高
hotter than the core of the sun.
你们觉得怎么样
How about that?
剩下的钱在哪
Where's the rest?
搞定了这个再给你们剩下的钱
You'll get the rest of your money when the job's done.
我派来的物理学家呢
Where is my physicist?
他拿到钱后 我们把他接过来
He'll pick up his money, then we'll pick him up.
他住在罗马的一家酒店
He's staying at a hotel in Rome.
我们会在一天内完成武器的组装
We'll need an extra day to configure the weapon, then it's all yours.
你们想杀掉多少犹太人就杀多少
Kill as many Jews as you want.
为我们的胜利祈祷吧 兄弟
Do you practice Salah, brother?
我收到款项 完成任务
I receive my payment, complete the project.
我就是干这个的 兄弟
That's my practice, brother.
很好
Very well.
纳沃纳广场 罗马
核科学家监控名单
伊斯坦布尔的
Who was that guy?
那家伙是谁
In Istanbul.
他似乎总是先我们一步
It seemed like he was a step ahead of us.
嘿 你打不打算告诉我
Hey, you gonna fill me in here or what?
有些坏人作恶
There's some bad people planning on doing some bad things,
我们要阻止他们
and it's our job to stop them.
关于维克多 你好像没说什么
You still haven't said anything about Victor.
维克多消失了 维克多不存在了
Victor's gone. Victor doesn't exist.
拉普 你觉得我们在这里是干什么的
What is it you think we do here, Rapp?
我们干掉那些该死的家伙
I think we kill people who need to be killed.
- 那谁来告诉你应该干掉谁呢
And who do you trust to tell you?
- 遵守命令就行了
I follow orders.
你想执行命令的时候 才执行命令
No, you follow orders when they suit you.
你加入我们
This whole thing is pretty much
只是实现自己目标的一种手段
just a means to an end for you, isn't it?
长官 我经历了很多事
A lot's happened in my life, sir.
- 是么
Really? Huh.
- 是啊
Yeah.
所以你觉得 我们派你到这来
So you think you were sent here
是为了给你人生中的遗憾 愤怒
as an outlet for your self-pity,
愧疚 找个发泄口?
and your anger, and all your guilt. Right?
爱国主义之所以还存在
Patriotism exists
是因为有你我这样的人为崇高的事业而奋斗
because people like you and people like me need a higher cause.
为了比我们俩更重要的目标而奋斗
Something bigger than us.
你脑子里你认为是"复仇"的玩意
That stink coming outta you
就是狗屁
you like to call "revenge," the rest of us call "shit."
如果你沉浸于其中
And as soon as it starts to feel good,
你就不再是一位合格的特工
that's when you stop being a professional.
那时候的你一文不值
And then what are you?
来说点好消息吧
Tell us something good, darling.
我们入侵了他们的系统
We're in their system.
一有人把钱从沙里夫的账上取走
The moment that transfer from Sharif's account is picked up,
我们就能马上收到消息
we'll know it.
你的笑容像红海一样美
Boy, you just smile, and the Red Sea parts.
地中海也很美啊
Works in the Med, too.
你太美艳了
I'll bet it does.
有人把沙里夫账户里的钱取出来了 两百万美元
Cash withdrawal from Sharif's account. $2 million, U.S.
扫描中
未找到匹配项
已匹配
发现那个物理学家了 我们走
There's our physicist. Let's go.
欢迎来到博斯科洛大酒店 祝您入住愉快
Welcome to the Boscolo and enjoy your stay.
谢谢
- Thank you very much. - Thank you.
他住1448间
He's in 1448.
我们住他隔壁
And we're next door.
- 密码
Code in.
- 维克多-查理 1109.
Victor-Charlie 1109.
已确认
Confirmed.
目标住1448房 我们住隔壁
Suite 1448. We're in 1449, right next door.
抓住那个物理学家 把他带出来
All right. We'll grab the physicist,
我去接应你们
and we'll take out whosever coming for him.
每15分钟给我打一次信号
Signal every 15 minutes.
嘿
Hey.
我听说了你的遭遇
I know what happened to you.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我很能理解你
I understand you.
比你认为的更甚
More than you know.
我知道失去我们所爱的人是多么的心痛
I know what it's like to lose people you love.
我们要把这些坏蛋绳之以法
We're gonna get these fuckers.
我靠
Fuck!
你们他妈的在哪呢
Where the hell are you?
赫尔利
Hurley... Where is he?
在哪里
I don't know what you're talking...
我不知道你在说什么
Where is he?
他在哪
He outside?
在外面
Please, no.
饶命啊
Please.
赫尔利 什么鬼
Hurley, what the fuck?
你不是在盯梢么 怎么没发现他们
I thought you were eyes on, why didn't you spot 'em?
他们比我们早到宾馆
They were already in the damn hotel.
当地的黑手党在与他们合作
Local mafia's working with 'em.
我会联系肯尼迪副主任 已经抓到物理学家了
I'll tell Kennedy we have the physicist.
刚才那边是什么情况
What the hell just happened out there, huh?
那家伙把我们的行动搞砸了两次
That's twice now this guy's blown up our entire op.
目标是什么
What's the target? Huh? What's the target?
- 我不知道 先生 - 说啊
- I don't know, mister. - Yeah, you do.
你以为我看不出来么
Do you think I'm stupid?
他是个美国人 他认识你
He's an American. He said your name.
是你训练了他？
Did you train this guy?
- 你喜欢抽烟么
You like to smoke?
- 我的天
Oh, Jesus Christ!
你抽烟么
- Are you a smoker? - I don't...
这习惯可不太妙啊
- Wait! - Bad habit.
慢着 我说我说
Wait, stop! Wait, wait! I know something.
- 什么 - 我说我说
- What do you know? - I know something.
他们称那个家伙为“幽灵”
There is a man... There is a man they call Ghost.
“幽灵” 那个伊朗人就是这么称呼他的
Ghost. I think it was an Iranian man said it.
他们在哪造炸弹
- Uh-huh. Where are they building the bomb? - I just...
- 他们在哪造炸弹 - 我只是拿了钱而已
- Where are they building it? - Took the money.
他们在哪造炸弹
Where are they building it?
再给你点时间好好想想
All right, here. Take some time to think about it.
就是那个“幽灵”么
Ghost. Is that his name?
为什么他要追踪你
Why is this guy after you?
是不是出于个人原因?
Something personal, sir?
他们在造核弹
They're building a nuke.
去纳沃纳宾馆
Hotel Navona.
洗个澡吧
- Clean yourself up. - Wait.
别走啊
Don't go.
美国总统命令美国海军第六舰队
America's president has ordered the Sixth Fleet
离开意大利那不勒斯的海军基地
out of the U.S. Naval base in Naples, Italy.
朝西南方向航行
The Sixth Fleet is now southwest off the coast...
我来帮你
Let me help you.
没事的 我自己来
No, it's okay. I'm fine.
还是我来吧
You're not.
你今天觉得如何
How are you holding up?
我今天很害怕
I was afraid today.
还以为我们都要丢命了
I thought we were going to die.
我要么一直很害怕 要么永远不害怕
Yeah, I'm either always afraid or never afraid.
我不知道我究竟是什么感受
I don't know which.
贴好了
There you go.
放松一会儿吧
Just relax now.
明天再去找“幽灵”
We'll search for Ghost tomorrow.
- 你吓到我了
You scared me.
- 你是谁
Who are you?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你之前说“幽灵”
You said "Ghost."
- 那又怎么了
What about him?
- 我从来没提过这个名字
I never told you that name.
赫尔利告诉过我的
Hurley did.
你就扯淡吧
Yeah, I think you're full of shit.
你到底是谁
- Mitch. - Who are you?
- 你有毛病吧 - 你为谁效劳
- Mitch, what's wrong with you? - Who do you work for?
我是中情局的
I'm CIA.
别他妈的骗我
Now don't fucking lie to me!
我没撒谎
I'm not lying!
你是伊朗人
You're Iranian, aren't you?
放开我
Get the fuck away from me!
你跟那帮伊朗人是一伙的?
Are you working with the Iranians?
说实话
Tell me the truth. Tell me the truth!
去死吧
Go to hell!
你是伊朗情报部门的么
You Iranian intelligence?
Are you Iranian intelligence?
关于幽灵 你知道多少
What do you know about Ghost?
我们需要解密装置
We're gonna need the decryption device.
你说的对 米奇
You were right, Mitch.
很难让这个伊朗间谍开口
This Iranian mole is a tough nut to crack.
我只从她那问到了她的接头人 阿扎德·阿沙尼
All I could get from her was her handler. Azad Ashani.
他是我的一个朋友
Happens to be a friend of mine.
我要去见见他
I'm gonna go pay him a visit.
- 我跟你一起去
Okay, I'm going with you.
- 不行
No.
我要你待在这
I need you to stay here.
肯尼迪带了一群中情局
Kennedy's on her way with the CIA team
和摩萨德特工过来
and a Mossad team.
她肯定会问我你去哪了
She's gonna ask me where you went.
我要怎么说
What the hell am I supposed to say?
没错 自己动点脑子
That's right, she is. And you're gonna be smart,
别说出去
and you're gonna keep your mouth shut,
掩盖我的行踪
and you're gonna cover my ass.
我还留着它呢
I still have it.
很不错啊
Very nice.
斯坦 见到你 我总是很高兴
I am always happy to meet you, Stan...
但是你每次找我谈的事 都让我高兴不起来
But never happy why.
下次我们见面的时候 可以去吃个比萨
Well, maybe next time we'll meet for pizza.
那个女孩子挺有骨气的
Your girl's tough, by the way.
对她好点
Go easy on her.
她是我的侄女
She's my niece.
嗯
Yeah.
你有什么消息要告诉我么
What have you got for me?
这件事的幕后黑手是罗斯塔米将军
The men behind all this are General Rostami,
伊朗参谋总长
our military chief of staff,
还有国防部长比赫兹
and our defense minister, Behruz.
两个人都很有权势
Both are very powerful,
都对禁核协议的签署心怀不满
and both are very angry about the nuclear treaty we made with you.
过去的两年内他们
They have been trying to acquire
一直试图搞到核材料
nuclear materials for the past two years.
他们找来了那个
And they are the ones
叫“幽灵”的雇佣兵
who hired the mercenary called Ghost.
罗斯塔米在德黑兰 比赫兹在罗马
Rostami is now in Tehran, but Behruz is here in Rome.
我让手下通过他的手机定位到他的位置
Annika has been tracking his movements through his cell phone.
他们在哪造核弹?
And they're building it here?
要是我知道就好了
I wish I knew.
我们抓住他们的物理学家了
We have their physicist.
他们没法做了
They can't build it without him.
但是
But...
那个雇佣兵
The mercenary asked Behruz
叫比赫兹找一个伊朗的科学家来
to use one of ours, an Iranian.
比赫兹同意了 他们匆忙行事
Behruz agreed. That was rash.
说明他们急于尽快完工
It means they are in a hurry.
他们的目标是以色列?
And the target's Israel?
我也想告诉你更多信息
I wish I had better information for you.
赫尔利在哪
Where the hell is Hurley?
告诉我现在是什么情况
You gotta tell me what's going on here. Now.
那家伙是赫尔利培养出来的么
That guy he trained, who the hell is he?
现在你不需要知道这个
That's not something you need to know right now.
你们在掩盖什么
What are you covering up?
当你有了足够等级的安全许可
When you've got a level-5 security clearance
有了20年的工作经验 再来找我谈这个问题吧
and 20 years' experience, talk to me.
要不然就闭嘴 乖乖干活吧
Until then, shut up and do your job.
我要你们解密并扫描她的手机
I want her cell phone decrypted and scanned.
当地警方一小时前在港口发现一具尸体
Local PD pulled a body from the harbor an hour ago.
胸部中弹
Gunshot to the chest.
死者是 伊朗情报官员 阿扎德·阿沙尼
Iranian intelligence officer, Azad Ashani.
我的天
Christ!
赫尔利就是去见他了
That's the guy Hurley went to meet.
这个混蛋
Stupid son of a bitch!
我觉得我们要去找到赫尔利的下落
All right, so what do we do? We gotta go after him.
他们在造一个他们的核弹 拉普
There's a fucking nuke in play, Rapp.
找到核弹是我们的任务 唯一的任务
That's the mission, and the only mission.
不管你怎么看
This is now a joint CIA-Mossad operation,
现在这是中情局和摩萨德的联合行动
whether we like it or not.
给我拨通局长的电话
Can you get the Director on the phone?
你就打算把他弃之于不顾了?
So you're just gonna write him off then?
这就是你的计划?
That's the plan?
斯坦·赫尔利几乎算得上是我的亲人了
Stan Hurley is the closest thing to family I've got.
要是他现在在场
And if he were standing here right now,
他只会问一个问题
his only question would be,
为什么我们要浪费时间去讨论他的问题
why are we wasting our breath talking about him?
没你的事了
You're through here.
你准备回程 这是命令
You're going home, that's an order.
现在给我坐下 闭嘴
Now, sit down and shut up.
为什么你要帮我
Why are you helping me?
阿沙尼已经死了
Your handler Ashani was killed.
赫尔利去见他了 突遭意外
Hurley was with him. Something happened.
我们要去追踪他们
I'm going after him.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
我们得动身了
We gotta go.
斯坦
Stan.
我等这一刻已经很久了
I've looked forward to this.
当然了 罗尼
I'm sure you have, Ronnie.
我要给你看点东西
I wanna show you something.
行啊
All right.
看看这是不是野蛮人的作为
Savages. Right, Stan?
但我不怪他们
But you know something? I don't blame them.
而怪你
I blame you.
如果你不违抗命令
Never would've happened
就不会这样了
if you would have followed orders, Ronnie.
你阵亡了 你就成幽灵了
"You go down out there, you're a ghost."
你就消失了
"You're a John Doe."
要是你被俘了
"You get captured?"
你还记得我说的话 我真高兴
Oh, you remember. That's very gratifying.
谢谢你
Thank you.
罗尼 你让我很自豪
You made me proud today, Ron.
你应该来救我的
You should've come for me.
你将更多人置于险境
Ten men would've died.
因为你他妈的没有遵守命令
You put 10 men's lives in danger,
你将更多人的生命置于危险之中
'cause you couldn't follow a fucking order.
- 去你妈的 - 去你妈的命令
- Fuck you. - Fuck orders.
重要的是我的性命
- Fuck the mission! - Fuck you.
我当时是你的手下 我信任你
This was me. I was your boy, I believe that.
你让我对你深信不疑
You made me believe that.
阿沙尼让手下
Ashani had their people tracking Minister Behruz's
追踪比赫兹的手机位置
secure cell phone.
我们找到了比赫兹 就找到了赫尔利
So, we find Behruz, we find Hurley.
米奇
Mitch!
看看你啊
Oh, yeah, look at that.
- 你是从阿勒颇的那些人那里学会这招的么
Did you learn that in Aleppo?
- 不
No.
斯坦 你教过我的 要让敌人出乎意料
You always told us what to expect, Stan.
现在告诉我你的手下在哪
Now, where's the rest of your team?
- 我的天 罗尼
Come on, Ronnie, really?
- 别再叫我罗尼了 - 你的手下在哪
Don't call me that. Where's the rest of your team?
你手下的那个新人 他一直在找我
Your new boy out there, he on my tail?
罗尼 这是你犯下的第一个错误
Ronnie, Ronnie, Ronnie. There's your first mistake.
审讯的时候 不要直入主题
You never start with a real question.
要循序渐进
You start slow.
进入到受审人的头脑当中
You get inside your subject's head.
斯坦 我再问你一次
Stan, I'm gonna ask you one more time.
你犯的第二个错误
There's your second mistake. Number two.
第二个错误 就是 不要说“再问你一次”这种话
You don't say, "one more time." You already...
妈的
Damn!
斯坦 我犯的第三个错误是什么
Now, what's that third mistake, Stan?
是什么
Huh? What is it?
来啊 继续啊
Go ahead! Go ahead!
我还有9个指甲呢 真爽
I got nine more! I like this.
真爽啊 再来啊
I like it. Go ahead, bring it on!
你个混蛋
You motherfucker!
他想知道我们外面是不是有人
Ronnie wants to know if I got a team outside.
对吧
Right, Ron?
能不能安全的将核弹运走
If it's safe to move your bomb.
是不是有人在跟踪我们
Are we being followed?
我的这个接班人在哪
Where's the new me?
我做了调查 我了解他的一切情况
I've done my research. I know all about him.
你是说米奇么
"The new me..." Oh, you mean Mitch?
我跟你说 米奇是个难以预测的家伙
You know, Mitch, he's unpredictable.
你算不准他的
You never know about Mitch.
他行踪不定
He might be here, he might be there.
跟你很像 但你更加疯狂
He's like you, but you're a real Section 8.
够了
Enough.
- 操你妈
Schizo mom.
- 他们在哪
Where are they?
- 你个没爹养的 - 他们在哪
- Loser dad. - Where are they?
我的天
God!
你的手下在哪
Where's the rest of your team?
- 去你妈的
Half-wit mom, psycho dad...
- 你手下的其他人在哪
Where's the rest of your team?
你这人渣 - 你手下的其他人在哪
- You're pond scum. - Where are they?
你这混蛋
Pond scum! You're fucking...
关于你接头人的事 我很难过
I'm sorry about your handler.
阿沙尼是我的叔叔
Ashani was my uncle.
肯定是比赫兹和罗斯塔米派人刺杀了他
I'm sure it was Minister Behruz
他们相对以色列发动核战争
and General Rostami who had him killed.
我们试图组织他们
They want nuclear war with Israel.
在和他们的斗争中
We tried to stop them.
我的兄弟和父亲双双丧命
My brother and father both died fighting them.
在这转弯
Corviale. Turn here.
你知道我最大的错误
You know what my real mistake was?
就是信任你
I trusted you.
你让我觉得我能干出一番大事
You made me feel like I was the Second Coming.
你就像我的父亲一样
And you acted like my father.
我信赖你 信赖美利坚合众国海军
I trusted you and I trusted the United States Navy.
美国做的事 都是正确的 是么 斯坦
U.S. of A. Does it, it's gotta be good. Right, Stan?
只是 从来都没人告诉我
Except
你所负责的究竟是一个怎样的项目
nobody told me the business y'all are really in.
你们制造出怪物
You create monsters.
这就是恶果
That's just what you do.
这么虐待我的人
Those people who did this to me,
你觉得他们是野蛮人么
you think they're barbarians?
扯淡
Bullshit.
我之前说的破解做的怎么样了
Where's the decryption I asked for?
我们开工前拉普把手机拿走了
Rapp grabbed her smartphone before we could get any of it.
目前找不到他
And we can't find him.
监控摄像头显示
Surveillance cameras picked up Rapp
他5分钟前打晕了我们的一个特工
taking out our agents five minutes ago.
你这是在干什么呢
What the hell are you doing?
这里发生的一切
There's not a single thing happening here
都是你一手造成的
that you didn't make happen.
上帝保佑这操蛋的美国 对吧
God bless fucking America, huh, Stan?
我不能告诉你米奇在哪
I can tell you where Mitch is...
斯坦 我犯的第三个错误是什么
What's that third mistake, Stan?
- 米奇.. - 我听不见你说的话
Mitch... I can't hear you.
我操
Fuck!
你犯的第三个错误 永远不要和敌人站的太近
Third mistake, never get too close.
赶快搞定你的私事
Finish your personal business here.
你的任务已经结束了
Your work is done.
炸弹已经装备好了
The bomb is armed.
- 启动计时器了么 - 是的
- Timer is set up? - Yes.
他在耍你
He's playing you.
炸弹是给他造的 不是给你的
Bomb's not for you, it's for him.
这只是他的计划罢了
It was his plan all along!
连不上网络
Dead zone.
这里收不到任何信号
We're not getting any signals here.
等一下
Wait a second.
你想拿核弹干什么
What are you gonna do with it?
斯坦 不是我要干什么
No, Stan.
应该是我们要干什么
"What are we gonna do with it?"
罗尼 为什么选择罗马这个地方啊
Why are we in Rome, Ronnie?
我喜欢罗马
I like Rome.
这里食物很好吃
It's good food.
永远不要以为 我会战死沙场
Never, ever thought I'd die in the field.
是不是觉得我很疯狂
Ain't it crazy?
我觉得我以后想
I always figured it would be, I don't know,
住在一个森林小屋里 带着我的狗
some cabin in the woods with my dog.
我的话嘛
Me?
我选择过水上生活
I think I want water.
死在海里大概是十分平和的
There's just something peaceful about dying at sea.
来吧
All right.
结束这一切吧
Let's get it over with.
不 你想痛痛快快的死
No, you'd like that, wouldn't you?
我不会杀了你的
I ain't gonna kill you.
斯坦 我要让你亲眼见证
You're gonna live to see
你一手造成的灾难
the crown of your creation, Stan.
数千美国人将会烧死
Thousands of Americans are gonna burn.
就因为你
All because of you.
好好观赏吧
Enjoy the show.
做好准备
Get ready.
启动倒计时
Go.
求求你救救我
Please help me.
安妮卡
Annika.
你的父母是好人
Your family were very well respected.
我是他们的朋友
They were my friends.
混蛋
Bastard.
我跟他们很熟
I knew them very well.
求求你
Please I beg you.
探测到一起爆炸
We've got an explosion detected.
在这
Here.
离菲乌米奇诺运河500米处
A half click off the Fiumicino waterways.
爆炸点位于地下
It's underground.
- 德尔塔一号小队 开始行动 - 出发
- Delta One, go! - Let's go.
我们坐直升机过去
Get a chopper out there.
拉普 你不应该来这的
You're not supposed to be here, Rapp.
你想怎样 把我开除?
Yeah, what are you gonna do, fire me?
那边还有一条通道 他搞到核弹了
There's another passage down there. He's got the nuke.
- 你一个人可以吧 - 快去吧
You gonna be good?
海军 救援直升机
Go. Go!
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
要不然她就死了
Or she's dead.
米奇 我要去见我的亲人
I want to see my family, Mitch.
不 安妮卡
No, Annika, you don't.
我要去见我的亲人
I want to see my family.
米奇 听话
Come on, Mitch. Be nice.
她想活命
She wants to live.
她想去见自己的家人
She wants to see her family.
放下枪
Put the gun down.
安妮卡
Annika!
核弹会爆炸的
The bomb can't be stopped.
你什么也做不了 就像那个在沙滩上死掉的女人一样
Just like you couldn't stop
你救不了她
that beautiful girl from dying on the beach.
艾琳
Irene.
核弹在那艘船上
The bomb's on a boat.
赫尔利
Hurley?
你怎么知道的
How do you know?
罗尼向在海上引爆核弹
Ronnie wanted to die at sea.
是不是第六舰队在附近巡逻
Is the Sixth Fleet out on maneuvers?
我的天
Oh, my God.
第勒尼安海 意大利
把侦察卫星都调过来
Bring up ISR feeds.
派飞机去现场侦查情况
Get me eyes in the sky over the coastline
通知第六舰队 发出核爆警告
and put the Sixth Fleet on nuclear alert.
汤姆
Tom.
目标是第六舰队 他们目前离海岸线25英里
The target is the Sixth Fleet and it's 25 miles offshore.
真是太耻辱了
It's a shame.
你女朋友生前最后看到的一幕是 你没法救她
The last thing your girl saw was you not saving her.
战斗警报
General quarters.
全体人员回到各自岗位
All hands, man your stations.
这不是演习 重复一遍 这不是演习
This is not a drill. I repeat, this is not a drill.
有一艘携带了核装置的小艇 正在接近中
Inbound, small vessel-borne nuclear device.
小子 赫尔利是没好好教过你么
Didn't Hurley teach you anything, little brother?
永远不要受制于自己的情绪
To never make it personal.
我可没有受制于自己的情绪
This isn't personal.
糟了
Shit.
核弹上装了计时器和起爆装置
The bomb has a timer and a release trigger.
炸毁小船会直接引爆核弹
We take out his boat, it'll detonate.
如果核弹在水面爆炸
If it goes off above the waterline...
那会是一场灾难 放射性物质会飘到大陆上空
Disaster. There'll be fallout all over the mainland.
这里是美国海军弗林舰 准备攻击
USS Flynn... Prepare to engage.
小艇转弯了
The boat is turning, sir.
谁在开船
Who's driving that boat?
那是拉普
Rapp.
去接他
Go.
- 长官您说什么 - 去接他
- Sir? - Go!
你在干什么呢
What are you doing? Hurley.
赫尔利
Hurley?
我想把他救上来
Trying to get our boy to throw the bomb in the water.
弗林舰 准备好了就可以开火
Flynn, you are clear to fire when ready.
别开火 小艇已经掉头了
Do not fire, Commander. The boat is turning.
不攻击的话 核弹迟早会爆炸
If we don't engage, that guarantees detonation.
我知道这风险很大
I understand there's a risk,
但这是我们最好的机会了
but this is the best chance we've got.
妈的
Shit! God damn it!
他在那呢
There he is.
调至海军无线电频段
Get me on that boat's marine bandwidth.
拉普
Rapp!
听到我了么 用无线电接听
Can you hear me? Pick up the radio!
把炸弹从船上扔下去
Throw the bomb overboard!
不行 我要带它离舰队远点
No way, sir, I gotta get further away from the fleet!
拉普
Rapp!
你他妈的这辈子 就服从我的命令行不行
For once in your life, take a goddamn order!
第六舰队要朝你开火了
The Sixth Fleet is about to blow you to hell!
指挥部 这里是德尔塔二队 炸弹落入水中
Command, Delta Two, the bomb's in the water.
指挥官 别开火 - 核弹落入水中
Commander, hold your fire! The bomb's in the water.
- 弗林舰 别开火
Flynn, hold fire!
别开火
Hold fire!
我们有30秒撤离
Got less than 30 seconds.
快 我们撤
All right, go! Get outta here!
我的天
Jesus.
注意 准备撞击
Brace for impact.
是 长官
Sir, yes, sir!
我的天
Holy shit.
抓稳了
Hold on!
坐稳了
Brace!
你就不该来救我的
You shouldn't have come for me.
你要习惯我们经常这么干 小子
Don't get used to it, son.
赫尔利
Hurley...
似乎我们能安全撤出去了
Looks like we're gonna be all right up here.
我是这么觉得的
I think.
请汇报受损程度
Damage control central. Report.
压力值正常
Pressure is normalizing.
船体多处受损
We have multiple hull breaches.
艾森豪威尔号 辐射值如何
Radiologicals, Eisenhower?
辐射值低
Low... Low levels.
启动清洁措施
Initiating countermeasure wash-down.
- 指挥官 伤亡人数多少
Commander, any casualties?
- 弗林号受损严重
The Flynn took some serious damage.
尚未收到伤亡人数报告 要是炸弹没有在水下爆炸
The casualty reports aren't in yet,
估计我们都完蛋了
but if it had gone off above the waterline, I don't think we'd be here.
艾森豪威尔号
Eisenhower,
愿上帝保佑你们
my prayers are with you all.
赫尔利 拉普在么
Hurley, is Rapp there?
等下
Hold on a minute.
是我 说吧
Yeah, go ahead.
米奇 你没事吧
You okay, Mitch?
没事 我挺棒的
Oh, yeah. I'm fantastic.
你今天拯救了很多人的性命
You saved a lot of lives today.
也有不少人牺牲了
Took some losses, too.
迪拜 阿联酋
What the hell are you looking at?
你干嘛这么盯着我看
You look like a mummy.
你看起来像个木乃伊一样
Yeah.
是啊
Well...
木乃伊可不用写这些报告
A mummy doesn't have to write up reports.
你口述吧 你挺擅长做报告的
Dictate them. You should be good at that.
罗斯塔米将军
Iranian official, General Rostami,
伊朗少数反对派领导人 在德黑兰
the leader of the minority opposition in Tehran,
声称他有证据表明 美国中情局内部
claims that he has proof that a secret group
直播 爆炸性新闻 袭击特拉维夫(以色列首都)的计划是中情局散布的谣言
罗斯塔米将军宣布竞选总统
有一个秘密暗杀组织
of assassins within America's CIA
应该对上周的核爆炸事件负责
are responsible for last week's nuclear event.
伊朗总统选举
With the Iranian presidential election
两周后即将举行
just two weeks away,
罗斯塔米将军受欢迎程度正在上升
General Rostami continues to rise in popularity.
他们说罗斯塔米将军
They say General Rostami is
是下一届伊朗总统
gonna be the next President of Iran.
是啊
Yeah.
他现在不必把以色列炸平 就能当上总统了
He didn't even have to blow up Israel to get there.
对我们来说 他还真是个大麻烦
He's gonna be a major pain in the ass, too.
拉普在哪 我联系不上他
Where's Rapp? I can't reach him.
我怎么会知道
How the hell do I know where Rapp is?
我只不过是个医院里的木乃伊罢了
I'm a mummy in a hospital.
罗斯塔米全力支持
Rostami has full support for restarting.
重启伊朗核项目
Iran's nuclear program.